let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The word Communication has come from latin word",
    answer: "Communicare",
    options: [
      "Communicate",
      "Communicare",
      "Share",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following will help an individual to become an efficient speaker?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "prepare",
      "practice",
      "perform",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "which of the following is not a type of non-verbal communication?",
    answer: "spoken communication",
    options: [
      "posture",
      "body language",
      "spoken communication",
      "paralanguage"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is visual perciption?",
    answer: "it is about having a prejudice view aout someone",
    options: [
      "it is about having a prejudice view about someone",
      "the experience of past events",
      "Both",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the correct passive form of this sentence-'He read a book.'",
    answer: "A book is read by him.",
    options: [
      "He has been reading a book.",
      "He is reading a book.",
      "He read a book.",
      "A book is read by him."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a kind of sentence?",
    answer: "Operative",
    options: [
      "Assertive",
      "Operative",
      "Exclamatory",
      "Optative",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many parts of speech are there?",
    answer: "12",
    options: [
      "8",
      "6",
      "12",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A paragraph has how many parts?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "5",
      "2",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is _____ price of bokk",
    answer: "the",
    options: [
      "a",
      "an",
      "the",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "I bought a beautiful dress at the mall.What is beautiful here?",
    answer: "Adjective",
    options: [
      "Noun",
      "Verb",
      "Adverb",
      "Adjective",
    ]
  },
];